Insisting they belong to a fourth class,
the "Fourth" is a group that resorts to
indiscriminate acts of terror to attain their ends.
They were attempting to spread a sketchy drug
called "monstrine" throughout the city of Libelle.
Invoke
[Flameshot]
Barrier
Sent by Pastor Sicilia from the church,
Momo and I started to investigate the drug.
Momo accidentally encountered Princess Ashuna,
who provided information on
the monstrine's production facility.
Meanwhile, I set out to investigate the figurehead
of the Fourth in the city, Manon Libelle,
and infiltrated an evening ball hosted by her.
But somehow,
I ended up having to bring this nuisance along.
Good evening!
I'm a pure, just, and strong priestess!
Enjoying yourselves?
Look, I'm a pure, just, and strong priestess!
Blessings to the both of you!
Akari, didn't I tell you not to stand out too much?
What? I'm not standing out!
It's a party.
I have to at least introduce myself to the
people I don't know or I'll seem odd!
Oh, honestly.
Even if someone talks to you,
you can't wander off with them, okay?
That, and don't have any of the food or drink!
There's no knowing what kind of suspicious
drugs they might be laced with!
I'm fine, you told me that like a hundred times!
What do you take me for, Menou?
Let's see...
I think you're an idiot with the brain of a ten-year-old.
That's not true!
A couple of elegant women just told me,
"My, what a lovely lady!" okay?!
That's me, a proper lady!
That kind of thing really makes me worried.
Still, I can't spend all my time worrying about Akari.
Akari, I'm going to excuse myself for a bit.
Really? I'll be so lonely!
If you're a lady, you shouldn't whine.
Anyway, wait for me like a good girl.
No moon tonight.
No divine protection from Saint Marta, I guess.
Episode 9: At the Evening Ball
You there, stop.
I said stop!
What's a priestess like you doing here?!
What a careless guard for a place
that produces monstrine.
All right, let's get this over with and go
savor the sight of Menou in a dress!
What I need to find is proof that Manon Libelle is involved
in the production and distribution of monstrine.
Indeed, the manner in which you
conceal your presence is impressive.
Instead of hiding yourself,
you keep yourself inconspicuous in plain sight.
It was so natural, even I almost failed to notice.
Who would have thought there would be another soul
attempting to infiltrate the castle during the ball?
Apparently Manon Libelle has plenty of enemies.
I'm a princess of the Grisarika Kingdom and
a knight in my own right, Ashuna Grisarika.
And who might you be?
One of my maids neglected her duties
to come meet with her lover.
I'm simply here to admonish her.
Pretending to be the daughter of an aristocrat?
No lady of the Noblesse learns how to act in stealth.
If so, it would mean Your Highness couldn't
be a lady of the Noblesse either,
given that you detected me.
The Order of Knights is an exception.
Strength must be chosen over grace.
Could it be you're of a similar ilk?
Why not turn around and show your face?
Of course.
Too shy to show your face, hmm?
I simply know my place.
I beseech you to turn a blind eye.
My apologies.
But, seeing a suspicious character
makes me want to cut them down.
Besides, it's obvious from your
bearing that you're a skilled fighter.
I prefer to scrutinize how strong
a person is with my own eyes.
So you ask that I fight Your Highness.
I'm glad you're quick on the uptake.
I suppose I have no choice.
Etheric guns.
They're supposed to be taboo.
The terrorists on the train had them, too.
Where are you getting these things?
S-stay away!
You were watching, weren't you?
A shot from that with your amount of
ether will just ricochet off of my barrier.
Anyway, why don't you show me
where your transaction records are?
Oh, and tell me about the etheric
tool producing monstrine.
I'll record it in my scripture.
Invoke
[Record]
If you're caught lying...
You know what will happen, right?
Not interested in a fight, eh?
Well, I'm going to enjoy this either way!
Invoke
[Gale]
Impressive judgement!
Invoke
[Flameburst]
[Gale]
I thought I was faster but she anticipated it...?
You're quite skilled at controlling ether.
Then how about this?!
From what I can tell,
this one doesn't have much etheric capacity.
This is no fun all alone.
How much longer is Menou going to be?
There!
[Gale]
Invoke
[Bubble]
I sense magecraft being conjured! Something big!
Bubbles?!
She used the bubbles as a diversion
while manipulating her dagger at will...
What smooth etheric control!
You got me!
It's been ages since someone went
easy on me or outdid me like this.
I'm touched!
I'm generous about repaying favors.
After all, I can't bear not seeing that face of yours,
whatever that might take!
I can't compete with her technique.
So I'll win using my advantage.
Double Invoke
[Slash: Expansion, Flameburst]
Invoke
[Gale]
What was that?!
What's going on? I see flames!
That's the way Menou went.
She's okay... right? It's Menou.
Yeah, she's got to be okay.
Menou!
Well, she got me.
To think she would get the better of me so easily.
Except for Menou, you can all just die!
Ah, so she's the one.
That's good material I can use
for poking fun at Momo tonight.
Something's wrong. Something's definitely wrong.
The weird feeling I had back there is getting worse.
I've regressed over and over again.
The only major thing that's ever happened in Libelle
was me getting sent into the Pandemonium.
But, this time...
Too many things are happening
that have never happened before.
Getting assaulted in the market,
this ball being hosted, that pillar of fire...
None of those have ever happened!
Good evening.
That was such a large pillar of fire.
Not to worry, though.
Both of them seem rational so
I'm sure there won't be much damage.
Oh, you must excuse my sudden appearance.
My name is Manon Libelle.
I do believe this is our first time meeting. Is that right?
This has never happened before, either...
Her coming to talk to me...
Honestly, could she be any more of a nuisance?
She's every bit the battle freak she's rumored to be.
That scuffle must have put the Fourth on alert.
It's a shame, but tonight's mission is over.
I should meet up with Akari right away.
Are you worried about who I am?
Please don't be. I'm merely a proxy.
It's just that...
I wanted a chance to meet with you briefly.
My own mother had black hair just like yours.
I would appreciate if you could tell me about the
place where you were before coming here.
This person knows...
that I'm an otherworlder who came from Japan!
Would you rather not?
No, that's not it.
Sorry, I don't remember.
It's true. I've lost most of them.
The memories of my sixteen years in Japan.
Is that so...
I see.
That must mean you've also
used your powers quite heavily.
I still envy you, though.
You have the thing that I long to have.
You possess the power to change the world...
as you see fit.
Sorry to have bothered you.
If you manage to get out of this city,
I do hope you will be free to live as you choose.
Something is definitely wrong.
With this many new things happening,
my advantage of knowing the
future won't matter anymore.
But, I have to save Menou this time for sure!
What to do? What to do? What to do?!
Oh dear. What's wrong with her?
No, calm down Akari.
Maybe this is a change for the better.
Either way, I need to figure out
what's causing these big changes.
To do that...
I'll look into that person who
seemed to know something!
For starters, at least.
What was the deal with those flames?
How scary!
Honestly. I told Akari to stay put!
Where did she go?
According to the transaction records,
they started producing monstrine two weeks ago...
Manon Libelle, who had done nothing until that point,
suddenly took initiative and brought in
the etheric tool for producing monstrine.
I wonder what could have happened two weeks ago?
The way this room is constructed...
It's a typical ritual space based
on the concept of original sin.
Which would mean,
the center of the room should have a coffin-
That's not a coffin.
An iron maiden?
That's a torture device.
I smell blood.
I see.
So this is the etheric tool used to produce monstrine.
What nasty taste.
They used... a child this little?
She probably won't make it, but...
Invoke
[Explosion]
Barrier
A conditional spell that activates
not when you open the iron maiden,
but only when you try to save the child...
Even worse, these spikes...
Damn this thing!
Poison on the spikes?
Seriously, whoever set that up has
a horribly twisted personality!
Have to at least...
Communication
contact... Me... nou...
With Miss Manon Libelle? Are you sure?
You mean that cute young priestess from before, right?
They were talking together.
Weren't they?
But, it didn't look like it was a very lively conversation.
Is it possible she was taken somewhere by Miss Manon?
It didn't seem that way. Right?
Yes. Once she was alone, she said,
"What to do? What to do?"
and was making quite a fuss.
That's right.
Then she wasn't kidnapped?
She was a cute girl but seemed a little "eccentric," don't you think?
Then where...?
Momo?!
Oh, I see.
That trap was activated?
I think it's finally going to come.
The day I get my revenge.
Isn't that right, Mother?
Me...nou...?
You don't have to talk, Momo.
I know everything that happened from the
recordings you sent from your scripture.
I'm... sorry...
There was a child... and I let my guard down...
You did a wonderful job, Momo.
I'm so proud to have you as my aide.
Take your time and rest up.
Don't worry. Leave the rest up to me.
Okay...
They've done it now, those Fourth bastards!
It was very strong poison and
she's not in good condition.
But the spread of the poison is slow,
perhaps thanks to her inherent reserve of ether.
I believe we can help her.
I understand.
I'm grateful for your swift and pertinent response,
Pastor Sicilia.
No need to be grateful.
Providing protection to priestesses
is the duty of the Faust.
And what of Ms. Akari?
I failed to find her.
It seems most likely that curiosity
tempted her to explore the castle,
where she must have gotten lost.
Either that or the Fourth have her.
They didn't seem to have any interest in Akari...
But of course that is a possibility.
As such, Pastor Sicilia,
can I ask you to close off Libelle Castle?
Momo's video recording has made it clear that
the Fourth are involved in the production of monstrine.
Let us completely weed out the Fourth based in Libelle.
I will invade the castle and capture
Manon Libelle and the leading members.
And recover Akari, of course.
Could I ask you to negotiate for the
Order of Knights to cooperate?
I'm surprised.
You rely on others, unlike Flare.
You're familiar with my Master, Pastor Sicilia?
She told me once to my face...
that I was useless.
I've met you before as well...
But of course you wouldn't remember.
By the way, Ms. Menou. Didn't you suspect me at all?
That I might have a hand in what's going on?
It would be a lie to say I never suspected you.
Especially since it's right after what
happened with Archbishop Orwell.
However...
I'm proposing this plan because I've determined
that you're trustworthy based on our interactions.
Pastor Sicilia, please give me the help I need!
Very well.
I shall go negotiate with the Order of Knights.
Libelle Island has been sequestered as of noon today!
All Fourth lurking on the island will be arrested
for the production and distribution of monstrine!
All who wish to plead guilty must surrender immediately!
I repeat!
Libelle Island has been sequestered as of noon today!
All Fourth lurking on the island will be arrested
for the production and distribution of monstrine!
Wh-who thought they would act so quickly?!
What do we do?!
C-calm yourself. They haven't arrested us yet!
You are completely surrounded.
This is unfortunate...
Do not resist and surrender immediately!
Perhaps I should make sure
the members won't talk, for starters.
Oh?
Did somebody touch this?
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
Let us discuss how to counter-
Oh?
My, it's amazing that you can do such a thing.
Perhaps it was you who snuck into my room as well?
Yup, that's right.
Hello again, Miss Manon.
I want to ask you a few things, but do you mind?
I bid you welcome, Miss Akari.
Next Episode
The Daughter of a Lost One
Next episode: The Daughter of a Lost One.